(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-29T02:17:37.099209",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
あいうえお菓子した
A-I-U-E-O, made of sweets,
かきくけこんなにも
Ka-Ki-Ku-Ke-Ko, so much too!
さしすせそソフトクリーム
Sa-Si-Su-Se-So, soft serve ice cream,
五臓六腑でいこう
Let's go with all our heart!
タッチついてタルト来た
Touch and a tart arrives,
なにぬねのりしお
Na-Ni-Nu-Ne, salted seaweed,
はひふへほっとパイと
Ha-Hi-Fu-He-Ho, hot pie with it,
みんなでぬくぬく
Cozy and warm with everyone!
ショートケーキふわり
Fluffy shortcake,
キャンディペロペロ
Licking candy all around,
チョコレートの川で
By the river of chocolate,
綿菓子雲見た
I saw cotton candy clouds,
アイスクリームと
With ice cream and pudding,
プリンのお城で
At the castle of sweets,
カスタードわたぬき
Custard watanuki,
二人のランデブー
Our two-person rendezvous!
パフェ色サンデー
A parfait-colored sundae,
あんこがハッピー
Sweet bean makes me happy,
たい焼きにクリーム
Taiyaki and cream,
小悪魔ドロップ
Little devil drops,
カップケーキから
From cupcakes,
苺あんみつまで
To strawberry anmitsu,
国境なきスイーツ
A borderless world of sweets,
仲良くなれるよ
We can become good friends!
ぼんやり夢見てごらん
Daydream a little bit,
キャラメルみたいにくっつこう
Let's stick together like caramel!
まみむめモンブラン
Ma-Mi-Mu-Me, mont blanc,
やゆよヨーグルト
Ya-Yu-Yo, yogurt,
らりるれロールケーキ
Ra-Ri-Ru-Re, roll cake,
わたぬきとキスを
And a kiss for watanuki!
あいうえお菓子した
A-I-U-E-O, made of sweets,
かきくけこんなにも
Ka-Ki-Ku-Ke-Ko, so much too!
さしすせそソフトクリーム
Sa-Si-Su-Se-So, soft serve ice cream,
のんびり早弁
A leisurely early bento,
焼きのりあぶって
Toasting roasted seaweed,
友達ほかほか
Friends are so warm and cozy,
もみじまんじゅうと
Momiji manju,
あんぱんお月さま
And bean jam bread moon,
わたぬきに始まり
Starting with watanuki,
わたぬきに終わる日々
Ending days with watanuki,
ほのぼの見つめてごらん
Tenderly gazing at it all,
甘くて苦い夕焼きを
The bittersweet sunset!
タッチついてタルト来た
Touch and a tart arrives,
なにぬねのりしお
Na-Ni-Nu-Ne, salted seaweed,
はひふへほっとパイと
Ha-Hi-Fu-He-Ho, hot pie with it,
みんなでぬくぬく
Cozy and warm with everyone!
まみむめモンブラン
Ma-Mi-Mu-Me, mont blanc,
やゆよヨーグルト
Ya-Yu-Yo, yogurt,
らりるれロールケーキ
Ra-Ri-Ru-Re, roll cake,
わたぬきとキスを
And a kiss for watanuki!
ミルフィーユワッフル
Mille-feuille, waffle,
ボンボンムースおにぎりパイ
Bonbon mousse, onigiri pie,
シュークリームバナナゼリー
Cream puff, banana jelly,
ババロアわたぬき
Bavarois, watanuki,
ホットケーキバウムクーヘン
Pancake, baumkuchen,
ワタヌキワタヌキ
Watanuki, watanuki!
バタークレープわたぬき
Butter crepe, watanuki,
ワタヌキワタヌキ
Watanuki, watanuki!
わたぬきとごはん
Meals with watanuki,
わたぬきとおやつ
Snacks with watanuki,
わたぬきと肉まん
Meat buns with watanuki,
わたぬきと北京ダック
Peking duck with watanuki!
みつめわたぬき
Mitsumame watanuki,
わたぬきシロップ
Watanuki syrup,
金時わたぬき大盛りわたぬきどん
Kintoki watanuki, huge bowl!
こんがり思い出色
Well-done memories in color,
はちみつみたいにとろける
Melting away just like honey!
わっぴーとペキンタック
Wappy and Pekintack
いつものわたのき
The usual Watanoki
わたのきシロップ
Watanoki syrup
金時わたのき
Kintoki Watanoki
お胸わたのきなん
Busty Watanoki
こんがり思い出色の はじめて見たみたいなとろける
Golden memories, melting like it's the first time
あいうえおかしした かきくけこんなにも
A-I-U-E-O sweets down, Kakikukeko so much
さしすせそとクリームソーダ レトロプレイこう
Sashisuseso and cream soda, retro play go
たちつてとぬけてきた なみのはねのりしを
Tachitsuteto slipped through, wave feather riding salt
はひふへほほんとばいと ふたりでろくろく
Hahifuheho really part-time job, the two of us rokuroku
まみむめもうんぷらーん よいゆいゆーきょぐると
Mamimumemo umplan, good yui yogurt
もみ胸もうんぷらーん
Momi mune mo umplan
良いユイヨーグルト
Good yui yogurt
なりりろりろおろききわたのきとキッシュ
Watanoki and quiche
わたのきのきとキッシュ
Watanoki's quiche
わたのきのあまみ
Watanoki's sweetness
わたのきのにもみ
Watanoki's bitterness
わたのきのさんみで すきすきロボコンも
Watanoki's sourness, and Suki Suki Robokon too
なーい！みんなお料理？
Na-i! Everyone, cooking?
おとライブ4期生姫森ルーナなのだー！
Oto Live 4th Gen Himemori Luna na no da!
みんな見に来てくれてありがとー！
Thank you everyone for coming to see me!
今日は素敵なゲストと重大告知があるので最後までおたのしみにー！
Today we have a wonderful guest and major announcements, so please enjoy until the end!
みんな、ルーナの演奏どうだった？
Everyone, how was Luna's performance?
ちょっとね、ミスしちゃったけど、がんばって弾いたのだよ！みんなどうだった？
I made a few mistakes, but I tried my best playing it! How was it, everyone?
みんなのちょっとコメント見るなら
Let me check everyone's comments...
最高だった？素晴らしい？
Was it the best? Wonderful?
ありがとー！
Thank you!
もう、なんかもう胸がいっぱい！みんな見てくれてありがとう！
Oh, my heart is so full! Thank you everyone for watching!
まずね、弾けたことと、まず最初、あのね、ルーナのね、このエレクトーンをね、みんなにね、見せたいなって思うなら
First off, I wanted to show everyone Luna's Electone that I practiced so hard on...
これすごくない？ルーナ仕様のエレクトーンなのだよ！これ、今日ののためにね、運営さんがね、用意してくれました！
Isn't this amazing? It's an Electone customized just for Luna!
Management prepared this specially for today!
見て、もうね、ちょっとみんなに1面を見てもらえたのら。見て、ここにホロライブって書いてあるでしょ？
Look, I want everyone to see every part of it.
Look, it says 'hololive' right here, right?
ここにもお月様とお星様がついて、それだけでもめっちゃちゃ可愛いのだ！呼ぶくない？
And it has moons and stars here too, it's super cute, right?
Isn't it adorable?
ここちょっと一周して、こっちもね、すごいのよ！
Let's go around once, this side is amazing too!
これすごいのさ！ルーナが使ってるね、マイクもね、あんなし！もうね、最高！今日ののためにね、ルーナの
This is amazing! Even the mic Luna uses is like that!
It's the best! For today, Luna...
今までね、練習してきたね、エレクトーンのね、発表会のために準備してくれました！
prepared it for Luna's Electone recital
that she's been practicing so hard for!
ちょっと、ここね、足のところスケロッドよ、ちょっと見てほしいのら。
Look at the foot pedals here, I want you to take a look.
見える？ルーナ見える？みんなルーナのこと見れてる？
Can you see? Can you see Luna? Can everyone see Luna?
こい！こゆいね！かわいいね！
Come here! So cute! How adorable!
で、今もね、すごいね、可愛すぎてもう、
Even now, it's so cute that I'm...
もう今すごい緊張しどきになのだよ。
I'm just super nervous right now.
まあこれね、ルナがね、今年のね、6月かからね、本格的にエレクトーンの配信ができるようになって、
Well, you see, starting this June, Luna began streaming Electone performances in earnest,
1年前はね、誕生日にピアノのね、お披露目をしたんだけど、
and a year ago, I debuted piano playing on my birthday, but...
まあ今年からエレクトーンができるようになって、
starting this year I've been able to play the Electone,
みんなにね、エレクトーン癒されるとか、エレクトーン配信大好きって言ってもらえるようになって、
and hearing everyone say how soothing the Electone is, or how much they love my Electone streams,
今日、この日ルナの誕生日祭でね、お披露目がね、できて、本当に、本当に嬉しいのだ。
and being able to showcase it today on my birthday festival makes me truly, truly happy.
もう今本当ドキドキが、やばい。
My heart is beating so fast right now, it's crazy.
ちょっとミスしちゃったけどさ、まあ、ご愛嬌なのだよ。いつも通りご愛嬌でちょっとね、ばれへん、ばれへんなのだよ。
I messed up a bit, but hey, that's just part of the charm. Nobody noticed, nobody noticed at all!
みんなのおかげで、今こうしてね、素敵なね、エレクトーンで演奏することができました。
Thanks to everyone, I was able to perform wonderfully on the Electone like this today.
いつもね、聞いてくれて、ありがとー！
Thank you so much for always listening!
これからもね、聞いてくれたら、うれしー！
I'd be so happy if you keep listening from now on too!
ありがとうねー！
Thank you so much!
では、ここからは、スペシャルな、ゲストが、待っているのだ！
Now, from here on, we have a special guest waiting for us!
次のコーナーに、行くのだーい！
Let's move on to the next corner!
ということで、ここからは、ゲストの2人が来てくれるのだー、どうぞ！
So, from here on, our two guests are going to come join us—welcome!
わー！きゃー！きたきたきたきた！きたきたきたきた！ありがとー！
Yay! Ahh! They're here, they're here! Thank you!
今日ね、このお二人に来ていただきましたー。お二人、ご挨拶どうぞ。
Today, these two have come to join us. You two, please give us a greeting.
じゃあそれより先に、おはスバ！ルナ、お誕生日おめでとー！
Then before that, Ohasuba! Luna, happy birthday!
わー、ありがとー！ありがとー！
Yay, thank you! Thank you!
はーい、ホロライブで一番闇を抱えたお姉さん、幽霊ちょこなのだー！ルナちゃんお誕生日おめでとー！ありがとー！うれしー！
Hii, I'm Yuzuki Choco, the most brooding older sister in Hololive! Luna-chan, happy birthday! Thank you! I'm so happy!
いやー、とゆーことで、ね、いや今回さ、ルナ様の誕生日ということで、いやーちょっとねスバルと私がルナ様のお願いけたえ…叶えたビューかなって思うんだけど。
Yeah, so, um, since it's Luna-chan's birthday this time, Subaru and I were thinking we'd grant whatever Luna-chan wishes for.
え、本当？
Eh, really?
そうだね。
That's right.
本当に、え、なん、何でもいいの？いや、何でもいいとは言ってないのだ。何でもいいの？なに、何がしたいの？ルナ様。
Really? E-even anything? No, I didn't say anything is fine! What do you want to do, Luna-chan?
え、じゃ、え、いっぱいあるんだけど、え、じゃあ、いっこだけ、いっこだけ、いっこ、いっこ！
Um, well, I have lots of things, but um, then just one, just one, one, one!
じゃあまず、ケーキ食べたいのだー。
Well, first, I want to eat cake!
お、いいね！スバとちょこ先生に食べさせてもらえるたーい！
Oh, that's great! I want Subaru and Choco-sensei to feed it to me!
しょーがないね、それでは…え？
Well, it can't be helped then. Now then... Eh?
ケーキ、いでよ！
Cake, appear!
わー、でかっ！ケーキでかっ！こんなにデカいの出てくる？めちゃめちゃでかい！
Wow, huge! The cake is huge! Does a cake this big come out? It's huge!
ルナ、魔法使えるからな。
Luna can use magic, after all.
おい、適当言うなよ！初めて聞いたぞ、そんなの！え、食べさせて、食べさせて！
Hey, don't just say random stuff! This is the first time I've heard that! Eh, let us eat, let us eat!
しょうがないな。おたんじょうびおめでとう！
Can't be helped then. Happy birthday!
じゃあ、ハッピーバースデー歌いながら食べさせてあげるか！歌ってくれるの？
Then, should we feed you while singing Happy Birthday? Will you sing for me?
ケーキはよ、スバル。
Hurry up with the cake, Subaru.
ちょっと待て、その前に、いでよ、フォーク！
Wait a second, before that—appear, fork!
おい、フライングベンジャミンがそこで、え？何の事故？
Hey, Flying Benjamin right there—eh? What kind of accident is this?
なに、知らねえよ！一度もにとったん？何よ、お前、早業すぎるねんのだ！
What, I don't know! You already took it? What, you're way too fast!
ま、だんだんだんだん、先、ちょ、待てよ！なんでなんで、誕生日の本に、より先に食べてるの？
Well, wait, wait, wait! Why are you eating before the birthday girl?
え、違う違う違う、違う、ちょっと、なんかこうして食べようとかしたわけじゃなくて、あの、いでよっていったら……
Eh, no no no no, it's not like we tried to eat it like that... when I said 'appear'...
せーの、ハッピーバースデートゥーユー♪ ハッピーバースデールナ！
Ready, set, Happy Birthday to you, Happy Birthday, Luna!
あ、ちょっと待って！ここで食べた？あ、待って待って、あ、顔かぶってる。
Ah, wait a minute! Did you eat here? Ah, wait wait, ah, it's covering your face!
え、ここちょっと、もう食べていい？
Eh, can I eat already?
ハッピーバースデールナ！あむあむあむ…おいしー！ふー。
Happy Birthday, Luna! Nom nom nom... Delicious! Phew.
一歳おめでとう！おめでとう！
Happy 1st birthday! Congratulations!
いや、一歳じゃねえから！
No, I'm not 1 year old!
一歳じゃないの？
You're not 1?
一歳じゃないよ！いやだって、ルナ去年も誕生日迎えたけど、0歳児だぞ。ガチ？
I'm not 1! Because Luna had a birthday last year too, but she's a 0-year-old. Seriously?
え、じゃあ0歳児なの？
Eh, so you're 0 years old?
そうだってば。
That's right.
何ドヤ顔して言ってんだよ！そんなことあるわけねえよな！な、なんだよ。
Why are you saying that with such a smug face! That's impossible! What is this.
じゃあ、ケーキも食べたし！
Well, we ate the cake too!
え、待って早くない？え、そんなの？
Eh, wait, isn't that too fast? Eh, really?
あーっ！待って、待って！お誕生日言わとくしね？
Ah! Wait, wait! Let's not mention it's my birthday, okay?
じゃあ、そういうことで。
Alright, let's go with that.
え、待って、え、待って！頭も頑張ってね。
Wait, wait, wait! Use your brains too!
いや、待てよ。
Hey, wait a second.
おい、語尾抜けてるぞ。待てよじゃねえよ！
Hey, you dropped your catchphrase! Don't just "wait a second"!
語尾抜けてるぞ、お前。
You're missing your catchphrase!
だーいじょうぶ！戻ってる！あいってぃーが、うん。
It's totally fine! It's back! The catchphrase, yeah.
おい、待てよ。え、待って、え、ルーナも2人にも食べさせてえのだけど。
Hey, wait. Wait, wait, Luna wants both of you to eat it too, though.
あ、終わった？
Oh, are we done?
え、食べさせてくれるの？
Wait, you'll let us eat?
たーべさせてあげる！うぇーい！やったー！
I'll let you eat! Yay! Woohoo!
うおれ！
Woah!
え、こわっ！待って！
Eh, scary! Wait!
ケーキを前にすると性格変わるの？あ、それ、危なすぎるぞ！
Does your personality change in front of cake? Ah, that's way too dangerous!
え、食べさせる気なさすぎだろ！あ、ほら、ほら、ほら、ほら、ほら！えい！
Hey, you have no intention of feeding us! Ah, look, look, look, look, look! Take this!
えー！
Yay!
おいしかったー！
It was delicious!
うおれ！うおれ！
Woo! Woo!
はい！
Here!
ほら、すばる、はよ食べて！
Come on Subaru, hurry up and eat!
え、入んない！入んない、んみゃ！んみゃ！
Eh, it won't fit! It won't fit, yum! Yum!
あー、食べさせてあげる子！食べさせてあげるからね！んまんまんま！
Ah, I'll feed you! I'll feed you! Nom nom nom!
うめえ！
Delicious!
うめえよ！おい、取れない！ちょっとせんせえ！
So good! Hey, I can't get it off! Teacher!
取れなーい！あ、すばる、ありがとー！
I can't take it off! Ah, Subaru, thanks!
ほら、ルーナちゃんも、もっとお食べ！あ、食べないの？んまんまんま！
Come on, Luna-chan, eat more! Ah, you won't eat? Nom nom nom!
ほら、顔出て食べれん！顔のなまクリームが！んまんまんま！
Hey, my face is covered, I can't eat! The fresh cream on my face! Nom nom nom!
何自分で食ってんだよ！
Why are you eating it yourself?!
なに自分で食ってんだよ！
しょうがねえじゃねえかよ！満足しましたか、ルーナさん？
Can't be helped, right?! Are you satisfied, Luna-san?
うん、満足したけど、まだ、ね、まだね、まだね、まだお願いしたいことがあるなら…
Yeah, I'm satisfied, but still, you know, still, you know, if there's still something I want to ask...
なに？もう1回聞いてくれる？
What? Will you listen to it one more time?
まあ、内容による…え？
Well, depending on what it is... Eh?
本当ね、ルーナ、すばるにね、告白してほしいの！
Actually, Luna wants Subaru to confess her love to her!
あ、告白しますね！
Ah, I'll confess right now!
うわー！おい！語尾抜けてるぞ！語尾抜けてるぞ！
Whoa! Hey! You missed your catchphrase! You missed your catchphrase!
え？ルーナにね、告白してもらって、その瞬間をチョコ先生にね、カメラでおさめてほしいの！
Eh? Luna wants you to confess to her, and she wants Choco-sensei to capture that moment on camera!
そんなんさせてほしいの！
She wants you to let her do that!
いー！
Yay!
いいのか？そんな人工的に作られた愛情で…え、いんです。いいんです。いんです。
Is that okay? With artificially manufactured affection... Eh, it's fine. It's fine. It's fine.
こいつ、今日、気合いが違うからさ。
This guy is extra fired up today.
まあ、しょうがねえな！
Well, can't be helped!
え、やった！じゃあ、せっかくだから、いい感じの雰囲気のところでね、やりたいのなら！外に出るなら！
Eh, yay! Then, since it's a special occasion, Luna wants to do it in a nice atmosphere! If we go outside!
おお、おっけー！よーし、みんな、行くぞ！
Oh, okay! Alright everyone, let's go!
はい！せーの！おいしょー！
Yes! One, two! Heave-ho!
すっごい綺麗！
It's so pretty!
すてきなところにきちゃった！
We came to such a wonderful place!
あれはロマンチックね！ロマンチック！
That's romantic! Romantic!
ロマンチックだな、ここ。すごいね！ここ、ここじゃないすの？
It's so romantic here. Amazing! Isn't this the place?
ええ、それはもちろんね。すばるに愛の告白をね、ルーナにしてもらいたいならよ。
Eh, of course. If Luna wants Subaru to confess her love to her.
よーし、帰ろう！帰ろう！帰ろう！帰ろう！えーと、怖い、怖い、今日めっちゃゴミ消えろ！
Alright, let's go home! Let's go home! Let's go home! Uh, scary, scary, today all this trash disappear!
なるほどね！はいはいはいはい。わかりました。まあ、ステーションだもね。1回ぐらいいいよ。
I see! Yes, yes, yes, yes. Understood. Well, it's a station, after once is fine.
え、最後じゃないよ、これからも歩くけど。あ、まあ、それはほんで、じゃあやりましょう！
Eh, it's not the last time, we'll walk more. Ah, well, that's fine, let's do it!
ちょっと待って！ちょっと待って、チョコ先生何？
Wait a minute! Wait a minute, Choco-sensei, what?
いやね、ここでね、いや、ただ普通にやってもつまらなーいってことで、ここからね、３つお題を出します！
Well, you see, just doing it normally would be boring, so from here, I'll give you three themes!
まずはね、第1段階、２人の距離が縮まっていくっていう感じでね、手と手ぶれ合うところ。
First is stage one, where the distance between the two closes, where hands brush against each other.
ああ、いい！
Ah, nice!
なるほど！そして第2！
I see! And then the second!
もちろんね、２人のハグも見たいかな？
Of course, would you also like to see a hug between the two?
あーチョコ先生、最高！そして最後に、３つめー！
Ah, Choco-sensei, awesome! And finally, number three!
３つめ？３つめ、３つめ、３つめー！３つもあるのか？２人のどっちかがおでこにチューすしゃん！
Number three? Number three, number three, number three! There are three? One of them kisses the other's forehead!
ええ！？それはお互いがもう仕様じゃないから、たぶんすばるの方も頑張れなくなっちゃう…
Eh?! That's not part of the specs for each other, so Subaru probably won't be able to try hard...
あの、ちょっといいとこにベンチあるのらよ。
Um, there's a nice bench over there, you know.
なるほどね、ここで出会って、え、ごめん、やばい、記憶なくなっちゃった。何するんだっけ？
I see, we meet here, and... oh sorry, oh no, I lost my memory. What are we doing?
であって、座って、手と手触れ合って。
Meet, sit down, and hands brush against each other.
そんで、ドキドキしながら、すばるから愛の告白をして、ハグをして、最後でどっちかがおでこにチューしたらいいんじゃないかなって、チョコは思うの。
Then, while feeling nervous, Subaru confesses her love, they hug, and finally one of them kisses the forehead, Choco thinks that would be good.
わかった！じゃあしましょー！
Understood! Then let's do it!
じゃあちょっとチョコ、カメラ撮って来るね。やった！
Then Choco will go take the camera. Yay!
え、チョコせんが取るの？
Eh, Choco-sen is taking it?
当然じゃん！さすがステーションの女王！
Of course! As expected of the Queen of Station!
いやもうお任せくださいよ、カメラアングルは。なるほどね！
Leave the camera angles to me. I see!
じゃあ座ろう、座ろう。
Then let's sit, let's sit.
そうか。
I see.
失礼しまーす。
Excuse me.
あ、すばる、隣…隣にいるよ、すばる。
Ah, Subaru, next to... you're right next to me, Subaru.
え、これはまだここは知り合いじゃないってこと？
Wait, so you mean we aren't acquaintances yet?
そう。
That's right.
だからもっと離れたとこ行こ。
Then let's sit further apart.
え、どこ、どこからモゾモゾするの？
Uh, where, from where do we start acting all fidgety?
いや、モゾモゾ、モゾモゾしな、あの、モゾモゾモゾモゾしな…
No, fidgeting, don't fidget—well, don't keep fidgeting...
なっ、ねえ、待って、どこ触ってんの！
Hey, wait, where are you touching?!
あ、なるほどね、分かりました。
Ah, I see. Understood.
はい、それではお二人とも準備はよろしくて？
Right, then are both of you ready?
うん。
Yeah.
それではこんな…
Then like this...
よし。
Okay.
可愛い。
So cute.
引き上げてくれたのね。
You pulled it up for me.
引き上げてません！
I didn't pull it up!
ちょっとね、今全ての気持ちを吐き出しながら…そう。
Just now, spitting out all my feelings... yeah.
よし、やるぞ！恥ずかしい！精神！
Alright, let's do it! So embarrassing! My mentality!
それではそんなスバルのの、はい、イチャイチャ告白まで3、3、2、1、1、アークと。
Now then, up until Subaru's sweet confession, 3, 3, 2, 1, 1, and arc.
あ、今日も疲れたなー！
Ah, I'm so tired today!
え、スバ…なんで疲れてるの？
Eh, Subaru... why are you tired?
待って、知り合いじゃないんですけど、あの、あの、誰ですか？
Wait, we aren't even acquaintances yet, um, um, who are you?
あ、あ、誰ですか？初めまして？初めましてって感じがいいよね。
Ah, ah, who are you? Nice to meet you? "Nice to meet you" vibe is good.
初めまして、あ、わっ、私、姫森ルーナと申しますが、ずっとあなたのことを見ていました。
Nice to meet you, ah, I—I'm Himemori Luna, and I've been watching you all this time.
あ、そうなんですか？えっと、いつどこで？どこから?
Ah, is that so? Um, when, where? Where from?
え、も、もう、生まれた瞬間からずっと見ていたのだよ。
Uh, f—from the very moment I was born, I've been watching you.
僕も。
Me too.
スバルの、そこで手をつなぐのか！
Subaru, holding hands right there!
スバルも、あの、なんか生まれた時から何かが、生まれた瞬間の脳裏に過ぎったのがこの顔だなってずっと思ってたところなんです。
Subaru, too, um, like ever since I was born, something—the thought that flashed across my mind the moment I was born was this face, that's what I've been thinking.
本当におかしなこと言うわけ…
Saying such strange things...
嬉しい！これは運命ってやつなのだ？
So happy! Is this what they call fate?
もしかしたら運命かもしれないです。
Maybe it might be fate.
嬉しい！何？本当ですか？ルナさん？ちょっと嬉しすぎて手が震えちゃうぐらいわ、あ…
So happy! What? Really, Luna-san? I'm so happy my hands are shaking, ah...
あの、何かついてますか？
Um, do you have something on you?
スバル、ついてますか？あの、スバルさんに触れてもいいですか？
Subaru, do you? Um, is it okay if I touch Subaru-san?
はい。おっと、ここるんが、手をベンチに置くのか、それとも、どうしたらいいんですか？その、どうしたらいいの？
Yes. Whoops, Kokorun, is she putting her hand on the bench, or what should I do? Like, what should I do?
手、触りたいな。
I want to touch your hand.
じゃあ手を繋ぎましょう。
Then let's hold hands.
いいんですか？繋げるかな？上手に繋げるかな？
Is that okay? Can we connect? Can we hold hands nicely?
なんで逃げるんですか？
Why are you running away?
触れている、触れている、体温を感じるよ。
I'm touching, I'm touching, I can feel your body temperature.
あ、本当ですか？スバルの温かみ、実はスバルもなんかこの体温から、なんだかルーナさんはとても素敵な人なんじゃないかなと思い始めました。
Ah, is that so? Subaru's warmth—actually, Subaru also, from this body temperature, somehow started to think Luna-san might be a really wonderful person.
本当に？
Really?
ちょっともう少し体温簡単なので外しませんか？
Since it's a bit too much body temperature, shall we let go?
嬉しい！
So happy!
スバルのセリフが棒読みなんだが。
Subaru's lines are so deadpan.
もっと、ここらへん込めて。
Put more feeling into it around here.
じゃあ、実はスバルも、なんかもうちょっと触れ合いたいなと思ったので、あの、ハグしてもいいですか？
Well, actually, Subaru also thought she wanted to touch a little more, so, um, is it okay if we hug?
まちゅよん！
Of course!
じゃあ、ハグしましょう。立ちましょう。
Then let's hug. Let's stand up.
あ、立って、立ちたいですね。立ちたいです。あ、スバル自分でも立ちたいです。
Ah, stand, I want to stand. I want to stand. Ah, Subaru wants to stand herself.
あ、そんな直立不動な、結構あの、だんだんだんだん胸を張ってだんだんだんだん感じなんです。
Ah, standing at strict attention like that, puffing out our chests more and more, that kind of feeling.
じゃあ、あの、失礼しますね。はい、いつでも。
Then, um, excuse me. Yes, whenever.
失礼します。あーー！スバルがそんな、あー！きゅんきゅん！
Excuse me. Ahh! Subaru is so—ahh! Heart-throbbing!
ルーナも、なんかもう離れたくない！一緒にいたいよ！
Luna also—somehow I don't want to part anymore! I want to stay together!
もうスバルがひたむきに生きてんのよ！
Subaru is living so earnestly here!
ルーナを見て！ルーナを見て！君のことが好きだ！本当？スバルと付き合ってください。
Look at Luna! Look at Luna! I like you! Really? Please go out with Subaru.
嬉しい！ありがとちゅ！
So happy! Thank youchu!
嬉しい！ありがとう！これからもよろしく。
So happy! Thank you! Let's get along from now on too.
よろしくね。よろしく。
Nice to meet you. Best regards.
はい、カット！カットカット！
Alright, cut! Cut, cut, cut!
どうでしたでしょうか？
How was it?
いやあね、
Oh my goodness,
いやチョコさあ、ちょっと、なんだろうね、普段見れないスバルとルーナちゃんがみれて、これはこれは面白いのかなって思っちゃった。
Choco-sensei here—well, being able to see Subaru and Luna-chan in ways we don't usually see, I thought it was pretty entertaining in its own right.
どういうところが面白かったんですか？
What part of it was entertaining?
スバルが棒読みで、ルーナちゃんが攻めの姿勢が変わらないんだが。
Subaru being deadpan, while Luna-chan's aggressive stance never changes.
勢いがすごいよ。
The energy is amazing.
あれ？そんなつもりはなかったんだけど、あれ？
Huh? I didn't mean it like that, though. Huh?
なんかね、その勢いが強すぎて、うん。
You know, that energy was just too strong, yeah.
なんかちょっと、なんていうんだろ、食われるみたいな感覚があった
It felt kind of... how do I put it? Like I was going to be eaten alive.
そんなことないよ！今日はね、なんだろ。
That's not true! Today, you know, how should I put it...
なるほどね！
I see!
そうなんです。
That's right.
え、じゃあさあ、あ、終わりじゃない？もしかして。
Eh, then, ah... isn't it over? Maybe?
じゃあ、ちょこ最後に、はい。じゃあ、るなたんが喜びそうなことしてあげるね。
Well, Choco, finally... I'll do something that Luna-tan will be happy about.
じゃあ、すばる、るなたん？
Then, Subaru, Luna-tan?
うん。座って。
Yeah. Sit down.
もう、このベンチトラウマなんだけど。
I already have trauma from this bench!
じゃあ、座ってみなって。
Come on, try sitting down.
いや、るなたん、もうちょっと近づいてよ。
Hey, Luna-tan, come a bit closer.
おまわりさん！
Police officer!
るなたんはじゃあ目を閉じて、るなたんの
Luna-tan, close your eyes, and on Luna-tan's...
肩に、頭置いて。
shoulder, put your head.
こてん。
Tilt.
首折れない？折れないから。
Won't your neck break? It won't break!
ちょっと王冠が突き刺さってない。
Isn't your crown poking me?
突き刺さないようにこうするから。あ、いいね、いいね！
I'll position it so it doesn't. Ah, nice, nice!
そしたら座るわ、るなたんの方を見て。
Then Subaru, look towards Luna-tan.
あ！いいわ、これ！あ！
Ah! This is good! Ah!
すばるが るなたんのおでこに、キスしてる！
Subaru is kissing Luna-tan on the forehead!
えー！これは！ぬくもりを感じるどころではないですよ！
Ehh! This is way beyond just feeling warmth!
ていうかいまの、しょこせんの声で耳に
Wait, with Choco-sensei's voice just now, in my ears...
なんて言ったの？
What did you say?
いや、ほんとうに。
No, really.
いやいいショットが撮れたわ。
Well, we got a great shot.
なるほど、よかった、よかった。ちょこ満足。
I see, I'm glad, I'm glad. Choco is satisfied.
ていうかちょこ先生が満足して、るなが満足するコーナーじゃねえのこれ。
Wait, isn't this a corner where Luna gets satisfied after Choco-sensei?
るな満足した？
Were you satisfied, Luna?
もうやばい。やばい。色々やばい。最高すぎて。
It's already crazy. Crazy. Everything is crazy. It's too amazing.
じゃあ、そろそろね、満足したところで最後ね。
Well then, since we're satisfied, finally.
最後ここどうするんでしたっけ？
What were we supposed to do here at the end?
ま、じゃあ、一回立ちましょうか。はい。
Well then, let's stand up once. Yes.
せっかくね、このね、ちょこるなが集まったということなので
Since Choco and Luna have gathered here...
ちょ、せん、あれだよ、こっち。おいで？
Cho-sen, hey, over here. Come here?
おいで？
Come here?
ということで
With that said...
ここからは3人で歌うたうなら！
From here on, the three of us will sing a song!
よし、じゃあ、いった部屋に戻るなら！オッケー！
Alright, then let's go back to the room! Okay!
じゃあ電車で行こう？
Then let's take the train?
オッケー！
Okay!
いこ、いこ！しゅっぱーつ！
Let's go, let's go! Departure!
しゅーぷ、しゅーぷ、しゅーぷ、しゅーぷ！
Choo-choo, choo-choo!
あんまり そわそわ しないで
Don't get so fidgety!
あなたはいつでもきょろきょろ よそ見をするのはやめてよ
You're always looking all over, stop looking away from me!
私が誰より一番
More than anyone else, I
好きよ… 好きよ… 好きよ…
Love you... love you... love you...
好きよ… 好きよ… 好きよ！
Love you... love you... love you!
星達が輝く 夜ふけ 夢見るの あなたの全て
On nights when the stars twinkle, I dream of everything about you
愛しても あなたは 知んぷりで 今ごろは 誰かに夢中
I love you, but you act oblivious, probably obsessed with someone else
ああ 男の人って いくつも愛を持っているのね
Ah, men have so many loves
ああ あちこちにばらまいて 私を困らせるの
Ah, scattering them everywhere and making me worry
ああ 男の人って いくつも愛を持っているのね
Ah, men have so many loves
ああ あちこちにばらまいて 私を困らせるの
Ah, scattering them everywhere and making me worry
あんまり そわそわ しないで
Don't get so fidgety!
あなたはいつでもきょろきょろ
You're always looking all over
よそ見をするのはやめてよ
Stop looking away from me
私が誰より一番
More than anyone else, I
あんまり そわそわ しないで
Don't get so fidgety!
あなたはいつでもきょろきょろ よそ見をするのはやめてよ
You're always looking all over, stop looking away from me!
私が誰より一番
More than anyone else, I
あまりそわそわしないで
Don't get so fidgety!
あなたはいつでもきょろきょろ
You're always looking all over the place!
よそ見をするのはやめてよ
Stop looking away from me!
私が誰よりいちばん
More than anyone else, I
私がいつでもいちばん あなたのすべてが
Love you more than anyone else in the world!
好きよ 好きよ 好きよ
Love you, love you, love you...
いちばん好きよ！
I love you the best!
ということで、ラムのラブソングを歌ったんだな！
So, we sang Lum's Love Song!
イェーイ！可愛いかったね！
Yay! It was so cute!
ねー！めちゃくちゃ可愛かった！
Right! Super duper cute!
魅力あったすごい二人とも
You both have so much charm!
なんでこの曲選んだの？
Why did you choose this song?
だってラムもっちだ二人愛されたかったからなのだよ
Because we wanted to be loved by Ram-mocchi!
ルーナが座ったらもう局の愛あげるわよ
If Luna sits down, I'll give you all my love!
え、ほんと？チョコちゃんじゃなくて？もっとちょーだい！
Eh, really? Not Choco-chan? Give me more!
ではでは、次のお歌に行きたいと思います！
Well then, let's move on to the next song!
え、もういくの？え、もう早いよスバル！
Eh, already? Hey, that's too fast, Subaru!
早いよ！でもね、ちゃんと段取りあるんだよ！段取りが！
Fast? Hey, we have everything planned out! There's a plan!
わかった！分かったなら次の曲の…
Understood! If you understand, the next song...
次の曲の場所に移動したら！
When we move to the next song's location!
次の曲の場所に行くためにみんな見月のほらなのだ！
To get to the next song's location, everyone look at the moon!
行くよみんな！見月に乗るのだ！乗るのだ！
Let's go everyone! Ride the moon! Ride it!
よいしょっと！おしりょっと！
Heave-ho! Oopsy-daisy!
こんな感じ？いい感じ、いくの？
Like this? Feels good, let's go?
じゃあみんな、しゅっこうー！いぇーい！しゅっこうー！
Then everyone, set sail! Yay! Set sail!
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our newborn excitement echo out
最高の時間、最高の仲間と
With the best time and the best companions
キラメキにのって
Riding on the sparkle
憶えてるかな最初の歌
Do you remember our very first song?
戸惑う声が震えていた
Our hesitant voices were trembling
ほんの少しあの日から続く未来は
The future continuing from that slight day onward
みんなと掴んだ今日だよ
Is today that we grasped together with everyone
もっともっともっともっと高鳴るハート一緒に行くよどこまでも
Beating faster and faster, we'll go together anywhere
アルバムの準備はOK？
Is the album preparation ready?
ひらけ夢の扉を 今ひらめきライダー
Open the door of dreams now, Kirameki Rider!
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our newborn excitement echo out
最高の時間、最高の仲間と
With the best time and the best companions
ここにいるよ見つけてくれたから
I'm here because you found me
君に会いたくてやってきたんだみんなで歌おう終わらないメロディ
Wanting to meet you, we came here, let's sing an endless melody together
キラメキ身にまとい
Clothed in sparkle
届いてかな 私の声
Will my voice reach you?
届けたいのは君に笑顔その笑顔が
What I want to deliver to you is a smile, that smile
理想の遠さに悔やんで
Regretting the distance from our ideal
みんなとなら笑ったね
We laughed together with everyone
ぎゅっとぎゅっとぎゅっと全て抱きしめて
Hugging everything tightly
一緒に行こうどこまでも アルバムの準備はOK？
Let's go together anywhere, is the album preparation ready?
すすめ希望の道を 今ひらめきライダー
Advance down the path of hope now, Kirameki Rider
好きな気持ちカラフルにからめていたいんだ
I want to intertwine my feelings of love colorfully
最高の場所、最高の仲間と
The best place, with the best companions
ここにいるよ幻なんかじゃない
I'm here, it's no illusion
君の心が幸せに染まるように重ねてくハーモニー
Harmonizing so that your heart is dyed in happiness
キラメキ身にまとい
Clothed in sparkle
歌い続けたいな 踊り続けたいな そんな願いがわがままでもいいでしょ
I want to keep singing, I want to keep dancing, even if such a wish is selfish, right?
だって楽しすぎて止まらない輝くステージでもっともっと
Because it's too fun and won't stop, shining on stage, more and more
楽しい 楽しい 愛しいだけじゃ直視できない
Simply being happy, joyful, and cherished isn't enough to look you in the eye.
今も 今も 悩みはあるけど
Even now, even now, I have worries,
ここにいるよ 私ここにいるよ
but I'm right here, I'm right here!
君と同じ世界を見つめて
Gazing at the same world as you.
きらめき舞い上がれ キラメキライダー!
Soar high in the sparkle, Kirameki Rider!
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heartbeat echo!
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
With the best times, with the best friends,
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
I'm right here, because you found me.
君に会いたくて やってきたんだ 見上げる歌を
Wanting to meet you, I came here, singing a song looking up,
終わらないメロディ きらめき身に纏って
an endless melody, wearing the sparkle,
きらめき纏って
wearing the sparkle...
はい！というわけで
Yes! And so,
きらめきライダーでしたー！
that was Kirameki Rider!
ルナ様大丈夫？
Luna-sama, are you okay?
大丈夫ちょっと...
I'm okay, just...
大丈夫なのなの？ルナ様も
Are you really okay, Luna-sama?
今日はルナが主役だからな！がんばってるのな！
Today Luna is the main star, after all! You're doing your best!
そうなのなの！今日はね、この三人でね、踊れてすごい嬉しいのな！
That's right! Today, the three of us got to dance together, and I'm so happy!
ね、ねこもうれし！まるでアイドルみたいだよ、すばるたち！
Right? Neko is so happy! You guys look just like idols, Subaru!
そうだよ！ルナとルナと...あ、ルナとじゃなくてアイドルだ！アイドルだ！そうだよアイドルだったわ！
That's right! With Luna and... Ah, not with Luna, idols! Idols! That's right, we were idols!
じゃあちょっとね、最後だからさ、これ最後な曲なんですよ、三人でやるのは。
Well, since it's the end, this is the last song for the three of us to do together.
うん、そう。
Yeah, that's right.
えー！早くない！？
Eh?! Isn't that too fast?!
え、写真撮ってくれるなら...え、まだ踊る！
Eh, if you'll take pictures... Eh, we're still dancing!
え、待って待って、まだ踊りたい！え、ちょっと...待って待って！
Eh, wait wait, I still want to dance! Eh, wait... wait wait!
え、じゃあさ、最後だからさ、写真撮るか！写真撮って...
Eh, well then, since it's the end, let's take a picture! Let's take a picture...
え、ルナのハート作れたのならハート！ハート？
Eh, if we could make Luna's heart, a heart! A heart?
ルナ愛されてる！
Luna is so loved!
しょうがないわね、これ...あ、いいよ！
Can't be helped, this... Ah, sure!
かわいい！え、フウダ様そんな、ハートの中に入ってもかわいい！愛されてるの、ルナ！はいチーズ！
So cute! Eh, Flare-sama, even inside the heart, you're so cute! You're loved, Luna! Say cheese!
いいじゃないですか！やったー！よゆう！
Isn't this great? Yay! Piece of cake!
じゃあね、おめでとうね本当に！おめでとう！
Well then, congratulations truly! Congratulations!
おめでとうルナ！ありがとう！
Congratulations, Luna! Thank you!
これからもがんばってね！うん、がんばる、この後もがんばる！
Keep doing your best! Yeah, I'll do my best, I'll do my best after this too!
じゃあちょっとすばるたちは退散しますか！そうですね！
Well then, shall Subaru and company take their leave? That's right!
また、またあとでね！またね！がんばってね！
See you later again! See you! Do your best!
またね、がんばってね、ありがとー！
See you, do your best, thank you!
バイバーイ！バイバーイ！
Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
はーい！すばちょこるなでしたー！
Hiiii! That was SubaChocoLuna!
みんな、おど、どうだったー？
Everyone, how, how was the dancing?
ちょっとコメント見る。
Let me check the comments.
3人のね、おど、おどダンスどうだった？可愛い？可愛かった？最高だった？
How was the three of us dancing? Cute? Was it cute? Was it the best?
大丈夫ね、お遊戯ね、頑張ったよー！
Are you alright? Like a kindergarten play, I did my best!
今日はすばちょころなでね、歌いたいってルナずっと思っててね！
Today, as SubaChocoLuna, Luna had always wanted to sing!
今日、夢が叶いましたー！
Today, my dream came true!
すばもね、ちょこせんせいも、一緒に歌って、踊ってくれて、本当に楽しかった！
Suba and Choco-sensei sang and danced with me, and I had so much fun!
本当にね、本当に二人とも、大好き！ありがとうね！
Truly, truly I love you both! Thank you!
あとはあれなのだよね、いまルナ、すぶに、告白されちゃったしね！
And another thing, Luna just got confessed to by Subu!
もうこれ愛されてる日ってことだよね、ルナね！
That means today is a day where Luna is loved, right, Luna!
えい！今日は最高の日なのだー！
Ei! Today is the best day ever!
あーい！
Hi!
ていうことで、
So,
ここからはグッズの告知の時間です！
it's time to announce our merch!
いきます、ででん！
Here we go, ta-da!
あーい！
Hi!
ふふっ、まず1つ目はね……
Heh, first up is...
かんざきひろパパ描き下ろしの……
Illustrated by Kanzaki Hiro-papa...
おっ、おっ、おっ、おっぱいマウスパッドなんだよー！
An opp... opp... opp... oppai mousepad!
やばい、やばい。
So funny...
照れたね、表情のルナはめちゃくちゃ可愛い！なーらるなかわいい！
Luna's shy expression is super cute!
ルナのねこの大きいおっ、おっ、おっ……おっぱいでね、
With Luna's big br-... breasts,
みんなのねこのおててをね、休めてほしいななのよ！
I want you to rest your hands on them!
そして2つ目は……
And the second one is...
ルーナイトの紋章マグカップ＆コースター！ででん！
The Lunaight Crest Mug & Coaster! Ta-da!
みて！
Look!
これの、このマグカップね、ルーナのモチーフとルーナイトっぽさあるのよね。
This mug has Luna's motif and Lunaight vibes.
これをね、考えたね、マグカップになったなら……
When I thought about it, it became a mug...
ほら、カップのこっち側がピンクので、取っ手がハートでね、めっちゃキュートなデザインにしてくれたのなよ！
Look, this side of the cup is pink,
and the handle is a heart, super cute design!
あとね、こちらのね、マグカップ＆コースターを、この下のね、オリジナルパッケージに入れてお届けします！
And we'll deliver this mug & coaster
in this original package below!
なんかさ、昨日ルーナさ、モザイク加工をして、みんなに見せて、
Like, yesterday Luna added mosaic censoring,
showing it to everyone,
なんかみんなさ、おパンツとかさ、おもちゃとかさ、言ってたけどさ、全然違うのだからね！
and everyone was saying "pants"
or "toys", but it's totally different!
このね、このオリジナルパッケージをモザイクかけたらみんなおパンツとか言ってたけど、全然違うからね！
If you put a mosaic on this original package,
people said "pants", but it's totally different!
なんなのら、こんなこと、こんなかわいいんだからね！わかった？
What is it, it's so cute! Got it?
ということで、そしてフルセットでね、こちらを購入すると、じゃん！
So, if you buy the full set, ta-da!
直筆サインとメッセージ入りポストカード、あとルーナのね、特典ボイスがついてくるならよ！
An autographed message postcard,
plus Luna's bonus voice!
こちらは本日22時からブースの方で販売開始するので、ぜひ手に入れてみてほしいなない！
Sales start today at 22:00 at Booth,
so please check it out!
いぇい！
Yay!
そして告知もう2つ目！いきます、ででん！
And announcement number two! Here we go, ta-da!
はっ！なんと！みんな！10月15日がすばちょくるーな1周年って知ってた？
Ha! What? Everyone! Did you know
Oct 15 is Subachocoluna's 1st anniversary?
ルーナもチョコ先生から聞いて知ったんだけど、びっくりなのだよ！
Luna learned it from Choco-sensei too,
I was so surprised!
ということで、その記念として10月ね、15日に歌ってみた動画をチョコ先生のチャンネルの方で公開します！
So, to commemorate it, on Oct 15
we'll release a cover song video on Choco-sensei's channel!
チェリーボムというね、かわいい歌を3人で歌ったので、ぜひね、初めての歌ってみた動画なので、3人のね、すばちょくるーなの初めての歌ってみた動画なので、ぜひ公開聞きに来てほしいなない！
We sang a cute song called "Cherry Bomb" together,
it's our first cover song, so please come listen!
そしてまだあと1つ告知があります。最後の告知は……ででん！こちら！
And there's one more announcement.
The final announcement is... Ta-da! Here!
なんなって？ルーナに新しいまるまるまる、まるまるが追加された！えっ、みんななんだと思う？
What? A new... was added to Luna!
What do you guys think it is?
えっ、なんだと思うこれ？
What could this be?
なるほどね、なるほど、うんうんうんうん。
Ah, I see, I see, mhm mhm.
こちらはね、明日の夜、みんなにねお披露目します！こちらのお楽しみにしていてください！
We'll reveal this tomorrow night to everyone!
Please look forward to it!
こちらものお楽しみにしていてください！
Please look forward to this too!
ということで、今年は素敵なゲストを呼んで、楽しい誕生日をね、過ごすことができました！
So, this year we invited wonderful guests
and spent a fun birthday!
そして練習してききた…
And practicing...
ピアノの発表会もできて
Being able to hold a piano recital,
本当にね、嬉しい気持ちでいっぱい！
I'm really, really filled with happy feelings!
本当にいっぱいなのだ。
Truly filled to the brim.
これも全部ね、応援してくれるね、
And all of this is thanks to everyone
みんなのおかげなのだ。
who supports me.
最高の誕生日ライブを、ありがとうね！
Thank you for the best birthday live!
みんな本当にありがとう！
Thank you all so much!
そして最後は、とっておきのルーナの可愛さを詰め込んだ曲を歌うので、
And finally, I'll sing a song packed with Luna's very best cuteness,
聞いてほしいなら！
so I want you to listen!
チェックのキャミソールを着て
Wearing a checkered camisole,
今夜…ねえ！遊びにいくわ
tonight... hey! I'm going out to play.
スウィートな服は宝物
Sweet clothes are my treasure,
君はす少し恥ずかしそうね
though you look a little embarrassed.
ハートのネイルのピンクは…
The pink of my heart-shaped nails...
ホントはちょっと、大胆よ
is actually a bit bold, you know?
12時過ぎのシンデレラ
A Cinderella past midnight—
もっと夢見せて もっとそばに来て
let me dream more, come closer to me.
tonight 二人きり
Tonight, just the two of us,
let's party !
let's party!
happy ! fancy baby doll !
Happy! Fancy baby doll!
love me ! fancy baby doll !
Love me! Fancy baby doll!
世界一可愛い子に生まれたかった
I wish I was born the cutest girl in the world!
happy ! fancy baby doll !
Happy! Fancy baby doll!
love me ! fancy baby doll !
Love me! Fancy baby doll!
何万回言われてもまだ不安だわ
No matter how many times you tell me, I'm still uneasy—
あ・い・し・て・る？
do you love me?
カートに溢れてしまうほど
To the point of overflowing the shopping cart,
きょうは…ねえ！お買い物の日
today is... hey! A shopping day.
スウィートな帽子と手袋
A sweet hat and gloves,
お洒落するとキラキラするの
dressing up makes me sparkle.
大きなハートがほしい
I want a big heart—
ホントはちょっと弱虫よ
though actually I'm a bit of a coward.
シープのブーツ脱ぎ捨てて
Cast off my sheepskin boots,
もっと愛される sweet girl 女の子
a sweet girl who is loved even more,
ねぇ 目指したい from my heart
hey, I want to aim for it from my heart.
happy ! fancy baby doll !
Happy! Fancy baby doll!
love me ! fancy baby doll !
Love me! Fancy baby doll!
世界一可愛いって今日も言ってね！
Tell me today too that I'm the cutest in the world!
happy ! fancy baby doll !
Happy! Fancy baby doll!
love me ! fancy baby doll !
Love me! Fancy baby doll!
何万回生まれても君に会いたい
Even if I'm born tens of thousands of times, I want to meet you.
本当よ！
It's true!
みんな！盛り上がってる？
Everyone! Are you hyped up?
今日のルーナ可愛い？
Is Luna cute today?
え？聞こえないのだ！
Eh? I can't hear you!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
もっと盛り上がっていくのだよ！
Let's get even more hyped up!
ハートのネイルのピンクは…
The pink of my heart-shaped nails...
ホントはもっと、大胆よ 12時過ぎのシンデレラ
is actually bolder... A Cinderella past midnight.
もっと夢見せて もっとそばに来て
Let me dream more, come closer to me.
tonight 二人きり let's party !
Tonight, just the two of us, let's party!
happy ! fancy baby doll !
Happy! Fancy baby doll!
love me ! fancy baby doll !
Love me! Fancy baby doll!
世界一可愛いって今日も言ってね！
Tell me today too that I'm the cutest in the world!
happy ! fancy baby doll !
Happy! Fancy baby doll!
love me ! fancy baby doll !
Love me! Fancy baby doll!
何万回生まれても君に会いたい
Even if I'm born tens of thousands of times, I want to meet you.
本当よ！
It's true!
今日はルーナのライブ来てくれてありがとうなのだ！
Thank you so much for coming to Luna's live today!
これからもずっとよろしくなのだ！バイバイ！
Please keep supporting me from now on too! Bye-bye!
ルーナイトへ
毎日嬉しい、楽しい日々が送れるのは
みんなのお陰なのらよ。
To Lunaite,
Being able to spend each happy, joyful day
is all thanks to everyone.
本当にいつもありがちゅう♡。
Thank you so much, always♡.
ワガママでマイペースなルーナのこと
これからもずっと見守っていてね。
As for selfish, easygoing Luna,
please keep watching over me.
大好き♡　2021.10.10
るーななのら♡
Love you♡ 2021.10.10
- Luna nora♡